time thinking about and
considering all of the
experiences that I've had and how I
reacted to one thing or another or how
somebody else reacted to one thing or
another and I I actually started uh
studying psychology when I was when I
was very young sort of as a
uh um you know the the same as one would
learn martial arts to defend their body
and of course their uh their their mind
as as well um
one studies psychology and studies
people uh in in order to figure out how
to how to best protect themselves in you
know the crazy world that we live in but
it wasn't just that I I found it really
fascinating how it was that that people
thought and how it was that I thought
and all of the little variables that
that piece together who we are and what
we
are and so
um back to your uh back to your original
question which I can't even remember
exactly what that was but um the uh the
the whole introspective thing has played
a massive massive part in shaping who it
is that I am today now with with that
being
said uh and it just as a question
because I think that uh a lot of would
would um and and kind of going back to
um your homeschooling and and how you
were raised because I mean it's kind of
a double whammy you know you were
homeschooled and you also had parents
that were in kind of the creative field
that you're in so you were you were
probably doing a lot of observation
around you you know know with seeing
what they what they've been doing so
what were some of the inspiring things
that you've seen with your parents and
how has their experiences shaped who you
are
well back to what I was saying before
about growing up in that environment I
mean I was I was sitting in the office
in in the in the in the conference room
with a with a coloring book
uh you know while uh you know while my
mom was having a meeting with the
executives from you know AMX and PepsiCo
and you know Fortune 500
Brands um and I didn't necessarily
listen to every single word I'm you know
I'm not saying that you know I you know
I I caught everything that was going on
but I got used to hearing that kind of
stuff I got used to those kinds of
conversations
I got used to that language being
spoken and because I was so young I I
absorbed the uh the the the context of
it I I learned and and understood uh
like I said to to think in the language
rather than just knowing the words of
the
language
and
so you know I'm I mean I guess you could
say that my first of you know
non-official internship was at the age
of five at a at an agency in New York
City um or at my at my dad's uh home
office or my mom's home office or or or
whatever but that was my classroom
growing
up and
so
those those experiences allowed me to
look at the world through
a very unique
lens but then at the same time I saw
everybody else around me kids my age who
were going to school for 7 eight hours a
day and they were sitting in a classroom
and they were dead
bored and they were
very restricted in a lot of
ways and then I would show up you know
free as a bird and uh you know i' i'
very very easily come across as you know
that that know-it-all jackass even
though I never meant that at all I you
know I have no desire to be anything
close to that um it's just that I
would I would bring
into into
conversation Concepts that people just
that people my age just didn't really
didn't really get uh simply because of
the the environment that that they were
in so let me ask you and then I have a a
question uh from the audience but um I
made a like a character ation of you at
the very beginning um not saying that
you were a Class Clown or you know a
rebel but you know you seemed when I I
look through because for
me I'm like you I honestly I didn't have
I wasn't raised in homeschooling but you
know almost I I wish I was because I
I've always been in my head cuz you know
being dyslexic
[Music]
hey what's going on folks my name is
Ryan Perez owner and founder of bow tie
creative and uh the hustle Zone mag that
is going to be coming out in um in a few
days in about 30 days uh it'll be
October 1st so um I first want to say uh
thank you guys all for tuning in to the
trivia we've been trying different
trivia
events um and we want to get your
feedback um in terms of uh you know what
we could do better to make those trivia
events on and popping because I know
when I don't have any when I don't have
much
content um to provide to people then
it's always nice to have uh a trivia
event and and you know and hang out with
you guys because we love you this is the
community this is live this is we're
live streaming right so you know what
better to to do things live than you
know to do trivia so um I I definitely
want you guys to tell me what your your
feedback is I know that Horus Mr Horus
you know Mr googler he always wins but
you know I think that it it feels better
that we have at least have somebody
winning than having nobody show up so uh
let me
know let me know folks if you um what
you guys think about the trivia I would
love to
um I would I would love to have you uh
have your
input and I made a mistake this is not
episode one I made a mistake but that's
okay we can edit that so the other thing
too is new line is coming out new
clothing line so hustle zone. clo if you
go there uh make sure you guys pick up
your your hustle hustle Zone t-shirts
because you know like all this stuff
costs money if you want to have a nice
like everything right if you're a
marketing company or you're in marketing
or if you're trying to Market yourself
you know money doesn't grow on trees I
you know I have some people that still
come to me say hey Ryan I want to I I
want to buy a website for
$250 can you do that for me uh no I'm
sorry I can't do it right now because
it's just really below uh what I can
afford to do that for and they're like
well I'll go to Wix then well go to Wix
because now Wix like Wix they're getting
so fast that they're starting to raise
their prices so go ahead go to Wix and
get the the cheap quality but let me
tell you Mr customer at the end of the
day I've never heard of someone making
$50,000 on a
$250 budget unless you're using Bitcoin
or your uh you know crack dealer or
something I don't know um so either way
you you know in order to support what
we're doing you need to buy the t-shirts
you need to support us uh you're going
to be able to donate um I put donate
links in the description please donate
like even it's $5 $10 help us build a
better platform for you so that we can
constantly engage you with really good
quality stuff so now here's the story
for tonight's show um and I I I am like
I have to tell my guest in advance that
um I'm
dyslexic and we all know I'm dyslexic so
when it comes to reading last names that
have a zed and an S it's so hard to
pronounce because it throws me off every
time I look at it I have to ask a few
times like how do you pronounce your
your name so I'm going to pronounce this
so is it
Zabo Zabo okay all right so you guys
couldn't hear that but he said yes
so tonight's show is about Christian
Zabo Williams okay uh and this is a guy
that has a very interesting
name for his his his company it's called
the visual company and I checked them
out you know he he's he's doing his
thing and and uh you look at his
personal uh uh Facebook profile and he's
he's nutty he's crazy this guy has
pictures of him making faces and all
this other kind of stuff and you're like
you know what he must be a rebel he must
be a rebel so he's he's probably you
know he's probably the the smart kid in
the class that's like you know what I'm
bored so let me uh change let me change
up my hair a little bit so you know and
let me just make a funny face in the
picture because I'm bored because you
know that's exactly what happens to us
entrepreneurs because I was that kid you
know I didn't have any hair though so I
remember in grade one I I took scissors
and I actually cut my hair so I had a
big bald patch on the side of my head
and then the teacher is like KES Ryan
Ryan KES what did you do to your hair
and I said I don't know I was bored I
had no clue I'm just too smart for this
damn class so um you know so he seems
like a that I could get along with so
we're going to get him on um pretty uh
pretty quick here but before we bring
him on please folks do me a favor I'm
going to share this out right now uh
please like and share share share share
share share share if I and I'm going to
be looking at comments in a pretty
pretty pretty minute here so just give
me a few seconds but make sure you guys
like and share so I'm sharing right now
and um I'm going to be sharing as well
oh thank you Horus for sharing um
Kiki Kiki Kiki says I didn't know how to
pronounce it
Zabo the S is
silent that's you know if I had a
girlfriend I'd be like if if that was my
last name be like so she's like what's
your what's your last name and I'm going
to be like it's Sabo the S is silent
right doesn't that sound
good so anyway um so we got anony says I
thought this was Star Trek you
need um I thought this was Star Trek and
you needed gold press uh Lum I have no
clue what that means but I will laugh
because it is
funny okay I'm joking Anthony I'm joking
man
um let's go okay all right and then we
got let Leticia in the house I think
she's in the house I don't know I'm just
getting these random notifications so I
got to share this to one more place and
then we're going to get our well you
know what let's bring our guest in so um
ladies and gentlemen I don't know
anything about this guy and we we did
have a few conversations via blab and he
was on Wei key and I don't understand
how he was on Wei key cuz I was on Wei
key um so I don't know how we didn't
become closer friends because how he how
he became a guest is that Horus is like
hey I know a guy that has a company I'm
like like hey I got a I got a hustles on
and uh and I introduce people that have
companies and he's like good you know
here's my friend so um I don't really
know his background story so this this
is what makes the show even that much
better um so please ladies and gentlemen
give it up for Christian what's going on
my friend hey hey how are you thanks so
much for having me oh man I'm I'm super
excited as you could tell I don't know
like probably in the pre-show you're
like man like this is going to be so
boring but uh I had to contain myself
because I didn't want to give the hustle
Zone experience away you know gotta get
it all concentrated for the moment yeah
exactly exactly so how are you doing my
friend so did you like the long long
intro yeah it was fantastic I loved it
it it has a it has a has a really great
uh flow to it it it it makes you want to
keep watching there's there's there's
more to be told there's more to be found
it's it's really great I like it yeah so
um so Christian we're going to start off
right from the very beginning and and my
guest they we've been doing this for
almost a year almost the year October uh
and we intered few people but our style
is a little bit different we first want
to know who you are before you became
who you are so you know my first
question to you is what's your
story my
story it start from the very beginning
very
beginning let's
see it was uh it was a sunny day in
[Laughter]
August um well I've I've
uh i' I've really been uh been an
entrepreneur from uh from day one um I
was uh I was homeschooled for the
majority of my
childhood and I grew up in
a family where my uh where both my
parents were entrepreneurs my mother was
the uh creative director of a of an
agency in New York City and my dad's a
marketing copywriter so I learned to
think in the uh in the language of
business and design
copywriting um really everything that
that goes into into creating a business
I was around that stuff from day
one and
so growing
up um I mean being being homeschooled
was was bad
enough but then uh you know on on top of
that being uh being in this environment
that was so different from all of my all
of my
peers it was um it was it it was a
little it was a little weird um and I
was I was torn in a lot of different
directions
and
so I
um I would say
that that gave me a lot of perspective
but also a lot of grief and
anxiety uh growing
up but I
um let's see the the The Story
Goes homeschooled for the majority of my
childhood I I did a brief stint in
public school uh I failed every single
class and I
uh every moment that I spent there
was me looking at this Market of several
hundred or a thousand kids that I could
you know try to sell something to and so
I was I was the one who was running the
uh the after hours school store because
it was only open before the uh before
the bell rang and I had a 3X search
charge on candy bars and pencils and I
sold gum which was very much frowned
upon um and I always I was always
finding some way to
uh to
um to to to bring to bring some kind of
value I I always really
liked or rather I I completely fell in
love with this idea that I could come up
with an idea and share it with
somebody
and you know that's that's a very broad
uh description but they would pay me for
it and I would see the smile on their
face when when they uh you know when
they when they got something that uh
that improved their life whether it was
you know a uh a much needed pencil for a
test or uh or later on when I was uh
when I was actually building uh building
businesses and so uh throughout the
years I I was always doing these these
entrepreneurial things I started my
first business when I was seven and that
was a uh that was a lemonade
stand and I uh I actually
um I talked two of my neighbors into
doing sort of a joint venture thing with
me and we were uh we were lined up on
the street one two three houses and we
were uh we were cross-promoting the uh
the lemonade stands to each other and
you know of course people not knowing
that we were all working together and so
we built ourselves a little uh little
summertime Empire there and that was fun
and
then noteworthy after that would be uh I
started my first internet business when
I was 12 which was a
subscription uh website for uh building
uh paper airplanes teaching kids how to
build paper
airplanes uh it was called build paper
airplanes.com
and I uh I put the whole thing together
with uh with my dad and we managed a
forum Community where we had discussions
about Aviation and uh creating really
Kick-Ass airplane uh paper airplanes
that actually flew because everything
that you got in uh you know in in the
book that you bought at Barnes & Noble
with the with the tear out paper and the
you know the the really thin high gloss
paper it didn't fly very well it wasn't
you know it wasn't really all that great
and the instructions oh my goodness the
instructions you know two big huge pain
points crappy paper
airplanes and instructions that you
couldn't
follow and so back to my my my reasoning
for doing things is I was always trying
to solve people's problems and that's
been both a blessing and a
curse uh in in many ways because on on
one hand I I like to help people that's
that's what I that's what I do that's
something that really matters to me but
then sometimes I might the try a little
too hard to to help people and then not
really be able to get anywhere because
it might not be my place and I've
learned the years of
course
but yeah so now and then going forward
word from that what what else has how
did you become to who you are
today
so
um I went through hell and back many
times um being in the environment that I
was in growing up in the family that I
grew up in it was really tough uh my
parents split up shortly before my third
birthday um and so that kind of split
the uh split the family Dynamic a little
bit
and they were they were kind of at at
odds over over many different
things and so that was a bit confusing
for me as as a kid uh growing up and so
my process throughout life life has
been essentially reverse engineering
everything that I grew up
around
and rewriting that script in my head and
redoing uh everything essentially to
change my thinking and to change the way
that I handled
things
and
effectively reshape who I would become
as as a person and I've gotten better at
it over the years uh and it's taken a
lot it's um it's it's been it's been
it's been tricky
but what turned me
into you know into into who I am today
has just been a a a
steady
um you know changing
of
uh or how how would I
say
um every every step that I went through
I would
always think about it I would I would
always try to like like I said reverse
engineer and take things take things
apart and put uh
kind of uh what's uh compartmentalize if
you
will all of my all of my
experiences so can I ask you a question
this is just an observation that I just
kind of picked up but um and first I
want to say before I even get to the
questions thank you guys all for tuning
in uh we got Gina uh hunter in the house
uh what's up Joseph with what's up Susan
uh Sonia um I think I said you know I
think I said you know uh we have Kiki a
lot of names so and then we Kiki we got
to get Kiki uh in the hustle Zone
because uh you know she's doing some
some great great great um things herself
um so yeah let me get back to the
question so the the question that I have
for you is that um you being
homeschooled you know and like I mean
homeschooling is great um and I don't
have any qualms I wish I was
homeschooled to be honest cuz I'm an
introvert um so I would I like I don't
really do well in in Social environments
for long you know I have like reserves
but you seem to be someone I'm not sure
if you're interviewed or not but you you
seem to be very
introspective and you know you you tend
to be it sounds like you're in your your
your your head a lot
uh trying to figure things out is that
is that a proper assertion that is
disturbingly accurate my
friend so and you know for and and it
has its great qualities but as and I'm
leading somewhere with this but it has
its grit qualities but it also has its
um it's downfalls because you know you
and I are pretty similar in that respect
uh and sometimes I get down on myself
and sometimes I don't feel like I'm good
enough to meet the expectations you know
cuz I know I'm different but I know that
being different sometimes you know
sometimes I have to make decisions where
it's not going to be in the view of
maybe in the positive view in other
people but I still have to do it because
that's kind of what I thought about do
you do you um do you uh have U any sort
of is there any sort of correlation with
what I just said with your
story um yes absolutely and and back to
my um fir first of all uh full
disclosure I am I am completely
exhausted and I tend I tend to run
myself around in circles trying to you
know put uh put the the the story
together as I go yeah um I've been I've
been working uh quite a bit today but
and and
just just in case you're wondering like
who who the hell is this guy and what
the hell is he talking about no man this
is entertaining this is awesome and
we're learning a lot about you so it's
awesome but the
um my
uh yeah as far as uh the whole the whole
introspective thing and and being and
being inside my my own head um that's
you know there there are a lot of uh
blessings and and and curses in in in
life you know sort of a uh What's the
phrase a double-edged
sword
um and
uh you know
I've I've
found a lot
of a l a lot
of very
um very heavily forced personal
development in shooting myself in the
foot by being stuck in my own
head um and I think through things a lot
sometimes I overthink them I've been
getting a lot better uh you know as I've
as I've grown up through my adult years
at not doing that um but it's still a
challenge because I'm an artist I I I I
nothing I do is ever good enough and I'm
constantly putting myself on this on
this pedestal and and
and and and setting these these goals
and having these expectations for
myself and I never settle for anything
less than than the best that I can
do and so I spend a lot of time think
thinking about and
considering all of the
experiences that I've had and how I
reacted to one thing or another or how
somebody else reacted to one thing or
another and I I actually started uh
studying psychology when I was when I
was very young sort of as a
uh um you know the the same as one would
learn martial arts to defend their body
and of course their uh their their mind
as as well um
one studies psychology and studies
people uh in in order to figure out how
to how to best protect themselves in you
know the crazy world that we live in but
it wasn't just that I I found it really
fascinating how it was that that people
thought and how it was that I thought
and all of the little variables that
that piece together who we are and what
we
are and so
um back to your uh back to your original
question which I can't even remember
exactly what that was but um the uh the
the whole introspective thing has played
a massive massive part in shaping who it
is that I am today now with with that
being said
uh and it just as a question because I
think that uh a lot of would would um
and and kind of going back to um your
homeschooling and and how you were
raised because I mean it's kind of a
double whammy you know you were
homeschooled and you also had parents
that were in kind of the creative field
that you're in so you were you were
probably doing a lot of observation
around you you know with seeing what
they're what they've been doing so what
were some of the inspiring things that
you've seen with your parents and how
has their experiences shaped who you
are
well back to what I was saying before
about growing up in that environment I
mean I was I was sitting in the office
in in the in the in the conference room
with a with a coloring
book uh you know while uh you know while
my mom was having a meeting with the
executives from you know AMX and PepsiCo
and you know Fortune 500
Brands um and I didn't necessarily
listen to every single word um you know
I'm not saying that you know I you know
I I caught everything that was going on
but I got used to hearing that kind of
stuff I got used to those kinds of
conversations I got used to that
language being
spoken and because I was so young I I
absorbed the uh the the the context of
it I I learned and and understood uh
like I said to to think in the language
rather than just knowing the words of
the
language
and
so you know I mean I guess you could say
that my first of you know non-official
internship was at the age of five at a
at an agency in New York City um or at
my at my dad's uh home office or my
mom's home office or or or whatever but
that was my classroom growing
up and
so
those those experiences allowed me to
look at the world through
a very unique
lens but then at the same time I saw
everybody else around me kids my age who
were going to school for seven eight
hours a day and they were sitting in a
classroom and they were dead
bored and they
were very restricted and a lot of
ways and then I would show up you know
free as a bird and uh you know i' i'
very very easily come across as you know
that that know-it-all jackass even
though I never meant that at all I you
know I have no desire to be anything
close to that um it's just that I would
I would bring
into into
conversation Concepts that people just
that people my age just didn't really
didn't really get uh simply because of
the the environment that that they were
in so let me ask you and then I have a a
question uh from the audience but um I
made a like a characterization of you at
the very beginning um not saying that
you were a Class Clown or you know a
rebel but you know you seemed when I I
look through CU for
me I'm like you I honestly I didn't have
I wasn't raised in homeschooling but you
know almost I I wish I was because I
I've always been in my head because you
know being dyslexic and not being able
to sometimes it's hard it was hard for
me when I was young to communicate what
I was thinking so I lived in my head a
lot you know I saw a lot of things that
a lot of the kids I you know I was
mature so I I it was really hard for me
to really interact with uh with it with
the with with with the the kids and it's
because I felt like I was Marty McFly I
thought I was on a spaceship somewhere
in you know uh 20 years ahead of time
and I was just waiting for people to
catch up you know and I I as a kid did
not feel
that I should dumb not even say that
they're dumb but to I didn't want to go
down to that level because I didn't feel
like I should I felt like people should
have come up with me because you know
what look it I'm not trying to expose
you to this new world of thinking
because you know it's it's it's great
for me but it's great for everybody but
people you know can only go learn at
their pace so it was pretty
isolating so my question to you is like
you know did you feel alone during all
of that
time um almost almost
entirely
um it
was yeah yeah I did
because I was always trying to find some
place
within I I I always wanted to to feel
like I like I belonged uh Community is a
really important thing to me I think
it's a really beautiful thing uh
Community effort uh Community Care
Community love um you know people coming
together and being together um and
setting aside the fact that you know
kids are just terrible terrible people
when it comes to that sort of thing in a
lot of ways yeah um you know and uh you
know that that all it all it all starts
with the whole uh you know boys have
coties girls have cooties kind of thing
um and then it just progressively gets
worse from there um but I always wanted
to find a way to fit in and and now
we're we're getting a little bit deeper
into my general psychology growing up
which was I always wanted to fit in in
some way I always wanted to belong in
some way but my way of thinking and the
way that I acted was so far outside of
what people would welcome with open arms
that I was the weird kid sitting in the
corner you know doing
whatever um and meanwhile everybody's
sitting over there in their group you
know snickering and and and pointing at
me you know saying you know like oh you
know who's who's this weirdo over
here and so yeah I was I was definitely
alone uh in in that regard for sure and
how did you and I like I guess I can
only I can only ask these questions
because I'm just basing it off of you
know just me being you know kind of
similar to you but for me I had to there
was a point in in my life cuz this is
not a negative thing I think some there
are some people that are are designed to
be
leaders and there are people that are
designed to be followers and I was I I
think that I was creatively designed to
be you know a leader and I had to accept
that I had to accept that I was not
going to be part of the The In Crowd I
wasn't going to be a part of any group
even though I had a longing for it but I
had to tell myself that you know what
Ryan if I have to be alone for the rest
of my life which is not true but you
know in my head that's how I felt it's
like if I'm going to be alone then I'm
going to go out with a bag and I'm going
to I'm going to put the best [ __ ] out
that human mankind could ever see as my
stamp because that's what it what that's
what mankind needs so if I'm going to
put out a hustle zone I'm G to make sure
that it's Crystal Clear it's going to be
the best art that you could possibly see
because it's you know being alone gave
me a lot of free time to create and to
build and now it's so like I feel like
I'm a master I'm so fluid in so many
different
avenues that it feels great because I
feel like I'm doing I have I have my
purpose so when did you realize that you
had a
purpose and that it's not about it
wasn't ever about you you know it was
about everybody trying to figure out how
to deal with you but when did you
realize you had a gift and when did you
realize that you know now you have a
purpose and that you you need to do
something about
it
um crazy
story that actually didn't come until
later um I was always sort of the odd
man out and always at odds with with
myself um very
um you know ve very uh very split
internal personality type of thing
where
I you know I I knew that there was
something more I just couldn't wrap my
head around what it
was
because the the the the collective sum
of everything that I'd been
through had really held me back in a lot
of ways so I learned all of these things
and I developed all of these skill sets
so understanding of business and people
and sales and design
marketing um building things that people
fall in love with all of
that um came together throughout the
years and I developed that throughout
the years but I didn't really do
anything with it because every time I
tried to St take a step forward it was
just you know just yanking me
back um something inside me just just
stopping me dead in my tracks and I I
was just I was just frozen I couldn't
move I couldn't I couldn't get to the uh
to the next step
um without without first hitting some
level of rock
bottom
and so you know the
uh uh the uh the the professional
psychologist would call this self-
sabotage right but really what it
was was me just not understanding my
self a complete and utter I mean a
disturbing lack of
self-awareness and not being able to
actually wrap my head around what it was
that I actually could
do and then on top of that actually
taking that step forward and doing
it mhm
wow that was that was what I was
starting at before where I was saying
pulled in so many different directions
it it it was like constant tension and I
was just supended I tried to go one way
I would get yanked back this way this
way get yanked back the other way
and it wasn't until very recently
that I was that that I I I managed to
dig a little a little
tunnel out of my own
head enough that I was able to
gain some better perspective of
myself and that came with
me actually listening
actually listening to those around me
and sure taking it all with a grain of
salt I mean anything that anybody says
to you take it with a grain of salt
because the things that you hear the
environment that you're in that all
influences you and what you allow in is
you know is is what's going to uh
dictate your your
state um
but I
uh it wasn't it wasn't until very
recently that I learned to just shut the
hell
up
and just
listen and then take all of that and run
the
equation
and for from
there that turned into
self-awareness that turned into me being
able to get out of my own
head
and
actually make some kind of a
[Music]
move and this this goes beyond
confidence like you know I'm confident
that I can do this so I'm going to do it
but when you're under that that kind of
tension that that centralized tension
that I that I that I
Illustrated it doesn't matter how much
you know about what it is that you can
do and what skills you have or what
gifts you
have getting to that
point of actually doing
it is the real challenge
and history repeats itself at least it
did for the longest
time I would start up something and I
would drop
it within I mean it could have been
hours it could have
been you know it could have been weeks
months maybe a year if I was really
lucky but
what the the point
where all of
that the point where
the where the damage
stopped was when I finally accepted the
fact that
I'm a hot mess okay I be able to focus
100% on one single thing ever my brain
is
constantly
everywhere no matter what it it doesn't
matter somebody could be having a
conversation with me I will be 100% in
that conversation and then just out of
nowhere just I'll miss an entire
sentence because I thought of like four
or five different things connected the
and then start trying to like reverse
engineer that and I was like oh wait a
minute I am so sorry I heard everything
that you said but that last part sorry
um you
know
and so it was the point where I
realized
that I'm not I'm not going to be able to
live up to that expectation I'm not
going to be able to hold
a job forever I I I I am the I am the
classic definition of entrepreneur a
chronically unemployable delusional
narcissist that I love that say that one
more can you say that one more time a
chronically unemployable delusional
narcissist oh my God that is the best
that is the best description of an
entrepreneur like everything you're
saying is like my words exactly uh we
have to get into the questions here so
um so we got a question here from just
to just to finish that that one last
point there yeah um it was the point
where I accepted that that was that that
was the
case and rather than letting that be my
downfall letting that be my failure I
turned that into my upside that's a
that's that's amazing man that is
amazing I think I think what a beautiful
story and thank you for being so candid
with us and allowing us to to to hear to
hear inside your head and to hear how
how you thank you for thank you for
tolerating my peace meal and then
eventually connecting us oh I think it's
amazing so we got a question from
Anthony Davis um so I'm going to put his
question up on the screen and Anthony
Davis says I have a question for
Christian how do you get people to take
you seriously when you first started how
did you get the um your clients and how
did you get people to take you seriously
because I'm sure that you being young
and you know a bit of a knowit all you
already know you've been there but you
know someone looking at you and like
well what does this kid know about you
know
marketing um that's that that's a that's
a really good question um and I know
that's you know that that's the that's
what everybody says when they get the
when they get the question it's like
H but really that that is a that is a
good a good question and I and I really
uh I really find that that interesting
um being taken seriously is really for
me at
least it's always been what I what I
bring to the table um you know I I know
what it is that I know and I'm very
confident in what it is that I know
and
I've you know i' I've tried to grab
things and just run with them and
sometimes I'm successful in that and
other times I run I I run straight into
a brick wall and just smash my teeth in
um but being taken seriously whether
you're just starting out
or you're you're a Season Pro really
comes down to you and and your your
passion and how how well you sell that
that vision and how well you're able to
connect your vision to that of a a
client somebody that you're working with
um and
so I mean I I I think that that really
that really answers the question is
being taken seriously
[Music]
is all about whether or not you're
actually worth being taken
seriously and I've
learned to not try to get people to take
me seriously about things that they
shouldn't take me seriously about it's
just not it's just not
smart um and there are some cases where
you can you know you can squeeze by a
little bit more you can you can get a
uh you know you you can you can kind of
uh I I I I don't like the phrase fake it
till you make it because you know you're
not really faking it because if you were
faking it you know you would immediately
be called on your [ __ ] and it
wouldn't be a thing there's always
something
there
um so it's it's really about whether
you're putting the right things in the
right place right we we have have a uh
we have another question here and then
10 minutes and then the show is done I
mean I could talk to you for hours go
yeah already wow this is insane I didn't
think you expected to come on the hustle
Zone like talking about all of this but
you know hopefully you'd come back as a
guest for
sure absolutely so uh Crystal day Chief
says so what advice do you give youth
who are like in high school that are
leaders but want to be followers how do
you get them to to see that and accept
it
um so I just just to make sure I
understand the question
that's someone who is put into a
leadership position but shouldn't be in
one so let me read this question again
so she says um so what advice do you
give youth that are like are are like in
high school I'm just reading what I see
so I apologize here like in high school
that are leaders but want to be
followers how do you get them to see
that and accept it so you know that they
are born leaders but you know they are
having to compro I'm I'm kind of
paraphrasing here having to compro
compromise who they are just so that
they can fit in and I mean like I'm
going to add myself before you answer
this question but I like Crystal I
honestly think
that we have to start embra like I think
that there's we have to get kids to
embrace
individuality and I think schools are
doing a really good job of doing that
nowadays uh but at the same time you
know we also have to teach kids how to
how to integrate because I think that
the most successful people know how to
be you know because a leader is a is
being able to Corral a group of people
together together and to focus on an end
goal or end Vision but then you have
people that are so in themselves that
they can't lead anyone you know and I've
had that problem a long time ago where
you know I'd hire people and they I'd
always fire them like you're fired
you're fired you're fired you're fired
fired and because I wasn't a really good
leader I was more of a manager I was
more of a guy that wanted control but
you know and I was really insecure but
you know you kind of have to know how to
be a team player you got to know how to
work with people because especially if
you're running a company everyone even
the secretary everyone has a role and if
she doesn't do her job or if the janitor
doesn't do their job then you're you
know that the whole company is screwed
so it's it's about knowing you know how
to be a team player but also knowing how
to be an individual and knowing when
your time comes to be a leader that you
stand up I don't know that is my opinion
about that question but uh what's what's
your opinion
I would say it's entirely about
self-awareness um and
that specific to
youth uh is a tough one to come by I'm
I'm a I'm a perfect example um I I would
guess Ryan that you were a perfect
example as well um youth
is I mean it it's a [ __ ] show it really
is yeah um and
so that that goes a lot deeper than just
you know a classroom lecture or some
words exchanged here or there um that's
you know that that's that's how somebody
is brought up that's that's how um you
know I'm I'm I'm still trying to trying
to get the get the question as as as
specific to to what I'm to what I'm
hearing
um
but you know kids kids who are
in um some sort of a a leadership
position uh if they're not built for
that then yeah they're probably going to
want to be a
follower just by default because that's
safe that's easier that's
comfortable
um and the one thing that I have done my
entire
life is everything to be out of my
comfort zone but at the same time you
know everything has its
contradiction I always wanted to be safe
but I wanted to push the envelope right
um
and
so that you know to what you were saying
Ryan
individuality is incredibly important
you can still follow if that's what's
right for you it's all about what's
right for you and that's where the
self-awareness thing comes in that's
right and so the combination of teaching
people to consider and to be
introspective and to pay attention to
all of these little things going
on um as well as imparting
wisdom um through experience and just
everything that naturally comes through
growing
up um you know that that's that's really
what it's going to boil down to yeah and
I I love I love the answers so we are 5
minutes till the show is done wow it's
been what pretty good show thank you
again uh Christian for for coming into
the hustle Zone and um a few questions
for you so we're on our second patch of
questions and they're quick so what's
your favorite
dessert favorite dessert yeah favorite
dessert that would
be ice cream
I mean well ice ice cream and cheesecake
and it has to be good New York
cheesecake not style
cheesecake no no no I want a guy named
Lou who talks about this over here and
that over there I want that guy to make
the
cheesecake that's real cheesecake fair
enough uh and uh ice cream Cherry
Garcia wow
wow very uh very uh specific taste
cheesecake fan all all but I've never
tried to your uh cheesecake because I
have never been to New York but that'll
be the first thing that I do when I get
there I'll try the cheesecake even
though I'm vegan I can have a cheesecake
I'll try yes can yes you can you're
allot you're allowed a little cheat here
just a little cheat so um uh rap or
rock say again rap or rock music
it really depends
entirely
um I've I've heard plenty of rock music
where I'm
like I've heard plenty of rap music
where I'm like wow those were some fire
bars and I like it and then I've heard
plenty of rock where I'm like I can jam
to this for hours so it all depends on
the
quality lyrical quality means a lot to
me the words that you say mean
everything and if you're just spouting
off garbage if you're just you
know what one thing that I can't stand
is uh is slant rhyming and and you know
modifying words that don't even rhyme
just to make a cheap rhyme um you know
and and not really putting any any true
creativity into into the lyrical flow
and and stuff like that and you know
that's all relative but I've heard
garbage from both sides and I've heard
gold from both sides so fair enough uh
and the last question I'm going to ask
you for the night before we close is if
you had a magic
wand um and you this wand could change
your
past what would you use it on and you
only have one wish
how would you change your P I guess
would be the the best
question I
wouldn't because
everything that I've been through in my
life has led me to right here right
now I'm doing all
right I've been through some
[ __ ] I've had good times I've had bad
times but the one thing that really
matters is that all of that brought me
to right here and right
now on the husta Zone okay folks on the
hustle Zone he was just going to say on
the hustle zone so
uh but uh so one more thing before we
before we close out is we do this as a
it's a tradition on the hustle Zone show
so I'm going to do a call and response
so I'm going to be welcome to the and I
need you to scream as loud as you can
and say hustle
zone
so so you're GNA have to you're gonna
have to wake everybody up and uh you're
going to have to scream as loud as you
can so welcome to the hustle Zone there
we I like that
my face though geez think I might have
melted a little
bit that that that that that was that
was awesome man shoot um so how can we
find you my
friend um you can find me uh anywhere on
social mainly Instagram Twitter Facebook
at csw
alive
and please connect with me of course
talk to me I'm not that guy who's just
like follow me and look at my [ __ ] no no
no I want to have real conversations
with people I want to actually connect
with people I want to jam with people I
want to make new stuff I want to build
things that people fall in love with and
I want to make today and everyday
remarkable
so there's that and
then my uh my little uh my little
company which we didn't really get a
chance to talk much about but that's
okay um because it when I when I said it
was a was a fledgling company like in
its infancy I mean really I just started
this up last week and I've been working
my face off for the last several days
just getting everything in order getting
everything set up getting out there
getting out of obscurity building a name
for the brand doing all that stuff and
you can find Visual company on Instagram
Twitter and Facebook at
VZ
Co and
the website is
vz. I got a four-letter doco domain I
was very proud of that that's awesome
that's awesome so yeah I'm sorry we
didn't get a chance to talk about it
worries but you know we're doing great
stuff photo Cinema creative shop based
on Heartford
Connecticut uh and we got like Susan day
is already saying friend me Christian so
I mean you got to you got people here
that want to friend you and thank you I
just want to acknowledge all the people
in the room uh and thank you again uh
Christian for being a guest on the
hustle zone so for having Ryan it's been
a pleasure thank you uh so folks um I
got two minutes two minutes past but
I'll acknowledge you before I leave
because without you um this wouldn't
this wouldn't happen so thank you to
Kiki thank you to Susan Dave thank you
to Frank sagasta
um thank you to Horus again for
participating there's no trivia tonight
uh and
uh thank you Anthony
Davis Mark
lill uh all those and then William uh
solasi Jr and all the people from blab
because this was a blab night you know
people are just zooming in CU I guess
for some people it's familiar faces and
uh yeah and folks hustle zone. clo make
sure you guys put on that t-shirt
because you're repping a culture you
heard it here first I am saying
entrepreneurialism is a culture it's not
just a way of life it's not a lifestyle
I'm an entrepreneur and I used I drove a
vol Volkswagen
Golf for
like till it broke down this year okay I
am the worst person to live that
entrepreneu lifestyle because I really
don't give um you know I don't really
give a [ __ ] about how how you look I
live the culture I breathe the culture
my man right here he lives and breeds
the culture it's in his head it's in my
head and what we do is we take it out of
our heads and we cure we give it to
everybody right so uh and people benefit
and then the economies stimulate and
they move forward so thank you guys all
for stepping into the hustle Zone hustle
Zone magazines coming out September F or
October
so I'll talk to you guys later and
writers all you writers out there that
said you're going to write for the
hustle
Zone September 10th is your
deadline so talk to you later bye I mean
see you guys later I didn't want to be
that angry but talk to you later